[{"aSentId": 4, "question": "i hate cold weather", "answer": "I hate it too", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "i'm culturally Jewish but don't consider myself particularly religious", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "it's complicated", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "no i'm an atheist", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "i had a really happy childhood and miss it a lot", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "my childhood was really boring", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "don't really know what to tell you about it", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "my favorite would have to be Pittsburgh", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "that's my favorite also", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "yes i go hiking all the time", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "yes that's why i take so many walks", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "not really i like staying inside more", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "yes it's very fast and convenient", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "no it's too slow and crowded", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "i prefer biking", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "sometimes unbearably so", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "never i'm always surrounded by awesome people", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "i would like to be your friend too", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "sorry i'm not interested", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "i have a huge family we're like 50 people", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "my family is tiny just  me and my parents", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "why do you have to go so soon", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "no don't go", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "yes it was amazing talking to you bye", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "awesome see you later bye", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "yes let's do that", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "i'd rather not go to the pool", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "let's go biking instead", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "yes i also don't care for it", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "really i love the cold", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "there's nothing better", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "i don't like them because i always get burnt", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "yes i completely agree", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "i'm not a fan", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "it's too hot out", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "yes i know i couldn't reach you", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "oh really with what", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "i was also really busy", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "what were you doing", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "yes it's a great day i agree", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "i'm not having a very good day", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "yes i'm Christian", "answer": "anything in particular making you happy", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Are you religious", "answer": "No I am not", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "do you feel lonely", "answer": "Some times but not a lot", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "we can go swimming and have some fun", "answer": "Sure lets go", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Do you like taking the subway to work", "answer": "Yes I do", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "My favorite city is Boston. What's your's", "answer": "Taipei", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "cool see you then", "answer": "See you", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Do you like nature", "answer": "Yes, I love it", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I go to church every Sunday", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Not really, but I celebrate holidays with my family", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I grew up in New York City", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "My family moved around a lot", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I was a very odd child", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "My favorite city is New York", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I like Boston, too", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Pittsburgh is the only city I've ever lived in", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "We need to take better care of the environment", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I love going hiking", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I really like animals", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I wish we had a subway in Pittsburgh for me to take", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Well, it beats driving", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Yeah, I like that it's a period of time I can read without being interrupted", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Taking the subway with co-workers is the best way to make friends", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Doesn't everyone, sometimes?", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Not really. I have plenty of friends", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Not right now, but often when I'm alone", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Aw, I'd like to be your friend, too", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Sure, we can be friends", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "No offense, but I hardly know you", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "It depends how you count. Three, I guess?", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I've got one sister", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I have about 20 cousins, but I don't see them very often", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Bye", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "See you later", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Same. Bye", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "See you", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Bye", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Have a nice day", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Sure, sounds like a good time", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Well, once it gets nice out we can", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I can't swim very well unfortunately", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Me too. I'm so done with winter", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I like the snow, though", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Me too. They make me so happy", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I know, don't they make everything better", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "It's so nice out today", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I know. And all the flowers are coming up", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I'm so excited that it's finally spring", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "It's warm, but it's still kind of gray out, don't you think", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Me too, there's a lot going on", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "What were you doing?", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Is something big going on?", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "yeah, it's going up to 70 degrees", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I don't know, it's almost too hot", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Yeah, I need to get outside more", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "04/19/2015 09:04:55,", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "No I am not", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I was a very naughty boy and always made my parents worrying about me", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Taipei", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Yes, I love it", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Yes I do", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Some times but not a lot", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Oh that is great. Nice to meet you.", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I have four.", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Bye bye", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "See you", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Sure lets go", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "I hate it too", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Me too, I love sunny days", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Yes, it is fantastic", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "What are you busy doing", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "I don't believe in god", "answer": "Yes it really is", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "how many family members do you have", "answer": "I have four.", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "the weather is so good today", "answer": "Yes, it is fantastic", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i was busy last week", "answer": "What are you busy doing", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i love sunny days", "answer": "Me too, I love sunny days", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "it is really nice talking to you bye bye", "answer": "Bye bye", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "Tell me about your childhood", "answer": "I was a very naughty boy and always made my parents worrying about me", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "it is a nice day", "answer": "Yes it really is", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}, {"aSentId": 4, "question": "i would like to be your friend", "answer": "Oh that is great. Nice to meet you.", "docId": "110117pmt", "qSentId": 322}]